[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "They can be hinge, movable, immovable, semi-movable, or ball-and-socket. What are they?", "correct_answer": "Joints", "incorrect_answers": ["Bolts", "Hardware for carpentry", "Joists"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who made the statue of King Richard I outside the Houses of Parliament in Old Palace Yard in London?", "correct_answer": "Baron Carlo Marochetti", "incorrect_answers": ["John Doubleday", "Sir George Frampton", "Joseph Edgar Boehm"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the Sun line of the human palm associated with in palmistry?", "correct_answer": "Fame", "incorrect_answers": ["Relationships", "Future", "Children"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many times per year is a healthy female guinea pig able to give birth?", "correct_answer": "Five times", "incorrect_answers": ["Twice", "Seven times", "Once"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Stephen Chow Sing-chi plays in these movies, and is also the director and writer of all of them, but one.", "correct_answer": "The Tricky Master", "incorrect_answers": ["From Beijing with Love", "King of Comedy", "Shoaling Soccer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If your opponent in the game gin rummy picked up the jack of spades and discarded the queen of spades, what could you conclude?", "correct_answer": "She probably is collecting jacks.", "incorrect_answers": ["She is about to gin.", "She doesnt know how to play gin.", "She most certainly is collecting jacks."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the popular movie The Shawshank Redemption Andy Dufresne has a poster hanging on his wall in his jail cell. Who is the famous actress on this poster?", "correct_answer": "Rita Hayworth", "incorrect_answers": ["Greta Garbo", "Jayne Mansfield", "Bette Davis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What disease takes the life of Nicole Kidmans character, Satine, in the 2001 musical Moulin Rouge!?", "correct_answer": "Tuberculosis", "incorrect_answers": ["Rabies", "AIDS", "Hepatitis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The fastest growing nail is on this finger.", "correct_answer": "Middle finger", "incorrect_answers": ["Thumb", "Index finger", "All nails grow at the same speed"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Strychnine poisoning produces some of the most terrifying and painful symptoms imaginable.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happens to Cheechs cousin and Chong in the marijuana field, at the end of Cheech and Chongs Next Movie?", "correct_answer": "They are abducted by aliens", "incorrect_answers": ["They are arrested", "They crash the Ferrari they stole", "They are attacked by wild deer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are several renditions of the famed Long Island Iced Tea, but almost all of the recipes call for this carbonated drink.", "correct_answer": "Cola", "incorrect_answers": ["Sparkling Water", "7-UP", "Soda Water"]}]